franklinplanner.com 2000-12-19

# Franklin Planner Online - Privacy Statement

Franklin Planner Online has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices. 

We are committed to protecting your personal privacy. Our Five Principles of Privacy summarize and clarify that commitment: how we safeguard your privacy, how we treat personal information, and what choices you have. We understand that for you to take full advantage of the benefits of this interactive medium, we must do what we can to ensure that your privacy is secure. 

**Our Five Principles of Privacy**

  * We do not disclose your private online communications. 
  * We do not use any information about where you personally go on Franklin Planner Online or the Web, and we do not give it out to others. 
  * We do not sell your registration information (name, telephone number, mailing address, credit card information, etc.) unless you specifically authorize us to do so. 
  * We use secure technology, privacy protection controls, and restrictions on employee access in order to safeguard your personal information. 
  * We will keep you informed about what we do with your personal information, and we will advise you if we change our policy.

**How Does Franklin Planner Online Use Registration Information?**

Franklin Planner Online's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use this information from the registration form to send our users information about the website. The user's contact information is also used to contact the user when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected during registration. We use this data to tailor the user's experience at Franklin Planner Online, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

**How Does Franklin Planner Online Use Cookies and IP Address Information?**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. 

**How Does Franklin Planner Online Work with Other Companies and How Do These Relationships Affect User Privacy?**

Franklin Planner Online contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. 

Occassionally we may share information with our sponsors and partners. We will share such information on an aggregate basis and will never reveal information about individual users of the site. 

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

**What is Franklin Planner Online's Policy Regarding  Posts on Message Boards?**

Franklin Planner Online makes message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in public message boards becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. Messages posted on private message boards are only revealed to members of the private groups. 

**How Does Franklin Planner Online Secure Information Entered by Visitors?**

We use industry-standard technology to keep your personal information and information you have entered into our site as secure as possible. We also have put in place privacy protection control systems designed to ensure that your personal data remain safe and private. 

Each and every Franklin Planner Online employee servicing the website is obligated to abide by this privacy policy. Employees who violate our privacy policies are subject to disciplinary action, up to and including termination. 

Only authorized Franklin Planner Online employees servicing the website are permitted to have access to your personal information and such access is limited by need. 

**How Do User's of Franklin Planner Online Change Information They Have Previously Entered and/or Opt-Out of Receiving Information?**

Franklin Planner Online provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request registration information. To change information at a later time either send email to [comments@franklincovey.com](mailto:comments@franklincovey.com) or change your selections on our options page. 

**Contacting Franklin Planner Online**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with Franklin Planner Online contact us by email at [comments@franklincovey.com](mailto:comments@franklincovey.com) or by telephone at 1-800-655-1492. 

**Please Note:  
** _FranklinPlanner.com works with a third party that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how Flycast manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to<http://www.flycast.com/about_us/about-privacy.html>._
